# Tricia Norris, MBA, CSPO, CSM

Email: tricianorris97@gmail.com | Phone: 804-614-6547 | Richmond, VA LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/tricianorris | Github: github.com/plnorris97 | Portfolio: plnorris97.github.io

# Summary

Full Stack Web Developer with extensive experience in marketing and two years wholly dedicated to two online properties. Effective at combining creativity and problem solving to develop user-friendly applications. A recent project was a MERN stack application using MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, and NodeJS. Proficient in collaborating with stakeholders, vendors and clients using Agile methodologies.

# Technical Skills

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, Wordpress, ReactJS, MongoDB, MySQL, CLI, NodeJS, MomentJS, Adobe CQ5, Figma, Git, Github, Heroku
- Agile Methodologies, Web Strategy, Project Management, Adobe CC-Photoshop, Email Marketing, Metrics

# <u>Highlights</u>

**Full Stack MERN Application** | github.com/plnorris97/getoutsiderva | getoutsiderva.herokuapp.com *Lead/Full-Stack Developer: Get Outside RVA* 

Get Outside RVA connects Richmonders and tourists to the outdoor activities and locations in RVA.

- Developed concept and managed set up of database, server, components, and deployment
- MERN stack: MongoDB, Express, React and Node; Reactstrap; Material Design Bootstrap

## Redesign/Redevelopment of Two B2B Websites | Genworth Financial

Product Owner: Index Institute, The LTC Source

The websites were redesigned to better provide product information/resources to agents in the field.

- Index Institute: Included 73 components and pages; Increased policy illustrations by 77%
- LTC Source: Included 83 components and pages; Partnered to develop Product Selector tool

### Work Experience

#### **Developer Apprentice** – Maxx Potential – *Richmond, VA*

4/2019 - Present

- Develop Wordpress websites to client specifications and customize theme as necessary
- Provide QA, operational, and maintenance support for clients either in Wordpress or another CMS

#### Marketing Manager – Talking Monkey Media – Richmond, VA

7/2018 – 12/2018

- Project managed client websites while coordinating between client, design, and developer resources.
- Managed client social media campaigns creating strategy, executing design, and reporting metrics.

#### **Principal/Head Marketer** – Norris Consulting, LLC – *Richmond, VA*

3/2016 - 11/2018

- Designed and built client websites using the Wordpress client.
- Developed client marketing plans to include strategic and tactical approaches.

#### Marketing Manager – Profiles (Capital One) – Richmond, VA

6/2016 - 12/2017

- Managed sales and trade show team projects in a cross-functional Agile environment.
- Partnered with Affiliates client development team to identify synergies in strategy and execution.

## Marketing Specialist – Genworth Financial – Richmond, VA

12/2011 – 4/2016

- Led redesign and redevelopment of two B2B websites in Agile environment using Adobe CQ5 CMS.
- Improved relationship with web and marketing teams-reduced web requests from 1-2 weeks to 1-3 days.

### Education

- University of Richmond, Richmond, VA Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp
- Virginia Commonwealth University, Richmond, VA Master of Business Administration
- Elon University, Elon, NC Bachelor of Arts